That's a Band-Aid at best.
(Sheldon:)The core problem is that Amy and Wil
do not like each other...
(Sheldon:)...which is baffling
because they're both crazy about me.
(Sheldon:)And I like them, which indicates
they're bright and interesting...
(Sheldon:)...and/or were on Star Trek.
(Penny:)Honey, you can't make people
like each other.
(Sheldon:)Not true. Leonard made me like you.
(Sheldon:)Let me tell you, that was a hard row to hoe.
(Sheldon:)Cheers, pal.
Ooh!
(Sheldon:)Boy, that is a treat that's hard to beat.
(Sheldon:)Get the Mad Hatter on the horn.
I'm having a tea party.
You might wanna pace yourself.
(Sheldon:)I drink tea all the time.
I think I know what I'm doing.
Far be it for me
to criticize a man with a full pubis.